# Character mapping table.
#
# The fonts supplied for the reader do not have the full 
# character sets that most fonts have. To work around this
# we have this table to map one character to another.
#
# This should really be specified on a per-font basis, and
# ideally BBeB Binder should be able to figure this out on
# its own, but for now this is the solution.
#
# <HTML Character>:<BBeB Character>

ă:ã